const questions = {
  questions:[
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'baa',
      font: 'kulitan',
      options: ['Bá-bâ', 'Ga', 'Ba', 'Da'],
      correctAnswer: 'Bá-bâ',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Bang',
      options: ['Gang', 'Sang', 'Bang', 'Yang' ],
      correctAnswer: 'Bang',
    },
{
  id: 3,
  question: 'be',
  options: ['Ngi', 'Na', 'Ka', 'Be' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Be',
},
{
  id: 4,
  question: 'Bi',
  options: ['Bi', 'Mi', 'Bo', 'Da' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Bi',
},
{
  id: 5,
  question: 'bii',
  options: ['Ya', 'Bí-Bî', 'Dá-Dâ', 'Lu' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Bí-Bî',
},
{
  id: 6,
  question: 'Bo',
  options: ['Bu', 'Be', 'Bo', 'Bi' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Bo',
},
{
  id: 7,
  question: 'bu',
  options: ['Bu', 'Bo', 'Ba', 'Be' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Bu',
},
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'buu',
    options: ['Gá-Gâ', 'Dá-Dâ', 'Wa', 'Bú-Bû' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Bú-Bû',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'daa',
    options: ['Bú-Bû', 'Ba', 'Ke', 'Dá-Dâ' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dá-Dâ',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'dang',
    options: ['Gang', 'Lang', 'Dang', 'Mi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dang',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'de',
    options: ['Mo', 'De', 'Ma', 'Ka' ],
    correctAnswer: 'De',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Di',
    options: ['Go', 'Da', 'Ni', 'Di' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Di',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'dii',
    options: ['Ngi', 'Dí-Dî', 'Bi', 'Yang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dí-Dî',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'do',
    options: ['Do', 'Go', 'Bo', 'So' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Do',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'Du',
    options: ['Du', 'Pu', 'Gu', 'Su' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Du',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'duu',
    options: ['Bang', 'Kang', 'Wu', 'Dú-Dû' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dú-Dû',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'gaa',
    options: ['Nga', 'Dú-Dû', 'Gá-Gâ', 'Ti' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gá-Gâ',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'gang',
    options: ['bang', 'sang', 'gang', 'nang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gang',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'ge',
    options: ['Nang', 'Mo', 'Ge', 'To' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ge',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'gi',
    options: ['Bi', 'Mi', 'Li', 'Gi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gi',
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'gii',
    options: ['Bi', 'Gí-Gî', 'Gi', 'Wi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gí-Gî',
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'go',
    options: ['No', 'To', 'Go', 'Wo' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Go',
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'gu',
    options: ['Ki', 'Kang', 'Nu', 'Gu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gu',
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: 'guu',
    options: ['Gú-Gû', 'Gí-Gî', 'Bi', 'Gang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Gú-Gû',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: 'kaa',
    options: ['Ke', 'Ká-Kâ', 'Ni', 'Si' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ká-Kâ',
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: 'kang',
    options: ['Le', 'Se', 'Sang', 'Kang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Kang',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: 'ke',
    options: ['Ke', 'Mi', 'Nu', 'Pa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ke',
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: 'Ki',
    options: ['Ni', 'Pi', 'Da', 'Ki' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ki',
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: 'kii',
    options: ['Bang', 'Kí-Kî', 'Nang', 'Pa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Kí-Kî',
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: 'ko',
    options: ['Mo', 'No', 'Ko', 'Lo' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ko',
  },
  ]
  };
  
  export default questions;